http://www.hartvilletool.com/privacy

Festool Sanders, Polishers, and Abrasives
» View All...
Turning Tools & Accessories
Turning Tools
Lathe Tools & Accessories
Turning Tool Sharpening and Supplies
» View All...
Router Bits
Router Bit Sets
Straight Router Bits
Spiral Router Bits
» View All...
Router Accessories
Router Tables & Accessories
Router Jigs & Templates
Other Router Accessories
» View All...
Saw Accessories
Table Saw Accessories
Band Saw Accessories
Miter Saw Accessories
» View All...
Sharpening Tools
Oneway Wolverine
Tormek
Robert Sorby ProEdge System
» View All...
Carving Tools
Flexcut Carving Tools
Carving Sets
Carving Knives
» View All...
Drilling
Drill Bits and Drivers
Drilling Jigs
Kreg Tools
» View All...
Marking & Measuring
Marking
Measuring
Other Marking & Measuring
» View All...
Hand Tools
Chisels & Gouges
Hand Planes & Accessories
Handsaws
» View All...
Glues
» View All...
Nail Sets & Punches
» View All...
Woodworking Hardware
Project Hardware & Kits
Jig Hardware
Cabinet Hardware
» View All...
Miscellanous Dust Collection
» View All...
Picture Framing
Picture Frame Joining & Fasteners
Mat Cutters
Picture Framing Accessories
» View All...
Planers & Jointers
Carbide Tipped Planer & Jointer Knives
High Speed Steel Planer & Jointer Knives
Planer & Jointer Accessories
» View All...
Air Tool Fasteners
» View All...
John Deere Blades
» View All...
Honda Parts
Honda Filters
Honda Blades
Honda Electrical
» View All...
Office
» View All...
Construction & Trades Books
» View All...
DVDs
Woodworking DVD's
Remodeling & Home Improvement DVD's
Construction & Trades DVD's
» View All...
Total Price
* If you have changed the quantity of any of your items,
please make sure to update the cart before checking out.
Total: $
› Checkout
Our Commitment To Your Privacy
We understand and share your concerns about privacy, so rest assured that we will not sell, rent, or trade your customer information with anyone else.
To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect:
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the HartvilleTool.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
Credit/Debit Card Information
(etc.)
On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:
Name
Address
Phone Number
(etc.)
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We offer gift-cards by which you can personalize a product you order for another person. Information you provide to us to create a gift-card is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
When you order through our website we will register you to receive our updates on new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose if you indicate you do not want to receive promotional email.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data Security:
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by choosing the "My Account" link located at the top of every page. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can also correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information on this screen.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
How To Contact Us:
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us. . If you are a customer living in a country affected by the European Union’s (EU) General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) you may have your personal data (as described above) removed from our system if you desire. To have your data removed you will need to call and speak with one of our Customer Service Representatives. You may reach us by calling 800-345-2396 (or 330-877-4685) M through Friday, between 8 am and 5 pm USA Eastern Time.
› Privacy Pledge
› Site Map
› Shipping Info
› International Shipping
› About Us
› Cal. Prop 65 Notice
› Mobile Version
Hartville Tool
Phone Hours: Mon-Fri 8am to 5pm EST 800.345.2396©2015. All Rights Reserved
Connect
